For those who are under the influence of this telecast, the influence of my voice,
it is time for prayer.
Distance is not a barrier -
whether you are here or there or anywhere all over the world.
Lord Jesus, help us to live according to Your Word.
Your Word says, 'Work and report'.
Help us to live according to Your Word, in Jesus Christ's name.
Father, I command all unclean spirits operating in your health, career - leave, in the name of Jesus!
Leave, in the name of Jesus!
All unclean spirits operating in your career, marriage, finances, future -
leave, in the name of Jesus!
Leave, in the name of Jesus!
Thank You, Lord, for Your deliverance.
I can sense God's deliverance touching you!
Be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
I can sense God's deliverance touching you, in the name of Jesus!
Yes!
Someone is being delivered there.
Someone is going through deliverance, in the name of Jesus!
In the name of Jesus Christ!
I command healing on you!
I command healing on you right now!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Lord, for Your healing.
I can sense God's healing touching you right now!
I can sense God's healing touching your family, finances, career,
health, neighbour, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Right now, begin to feel the touch - God touching you.
Feel it!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Feel it!
Begin to cover yourself with the Blood of Jesus.
Cover yourself with the Blood of Jesus!
Cover your family, home, career with the Blood of Jesus.
Right now, cover yourself with the Blood of Jesus!
Cover your marriage with the Blood of Jesus.
In Jesus Christ's name we pray!
TT: Anonymous
RV: Mel Flowers 24/02/2019